忠告しよう…　１つ 本当の「幻影旅団」の証しには クモの中に 団員ナンバーが刻まれている。
Consider this a warning... First, a real Phantom Troupe tattoo has the
member's number on the spider.
２つ 奴らは殺した人間の数なんか いちいち数えちゃいない。
Second, they don't bother counting
how many they've killed.
３つ　二度と「旅団」の名を かたらぬことだ。
Third, never mention the Troupe again.
さもないと 私が　お前を殺す。
If you do, I'll kill you.
第４戦に名乗りを上げた レオリオ
Leorio has volunteered for
the fourth round.
ここで勝てば ゴン達の勝利が決まる
If he wins, the group's victory is assured.
だが　果たして…
But can he win?
さぁ！ 俺でケリをつけてやるぜ！
Okay! I'll finish up the job.
さっさと　そいつを片付けて 次の野郎を出しな！
Toss that guy out, and send in
your next competitor!
何だと？
We can't do that. What's that?
まだ決着が　ついていないから。
We can't move him yet, because his match hasn't been settled.
決着が　ついてないだと？ どういうことだ!?
The match hasn't been settled? What do you mean?
彼は　まだ生きている 気絶しているだけ。
He's still alive. He was only knocked out.
一方が　負けを宣言するか 死ぬかするまで 戦うと決めたはずよ。
This was a death match. The fight doesn't end until one
contestant surrenders or dies.
彼は　まだ生きているし 負けも宣言していない。
He's still alive, and he
hasn't surrendered.
ケッ　屁理屈ぬかしやがって。
Tsk... Damned technicalities!
けど あいつの　いってることは正しい。
But she's right.
俺も　そう思う。 ぐぐ…　そうかい。
I agree. I see...
おい　クラピカ！
Hey, Kurapika!
あの　死に損ないに 引導を渡して来いよ！
Go finish off that worthless trash.
断る。
I refuse.
あ？　何でだよ!?
Huh? Why?!
勝負は　もう　ついていた。
The fight is over.
あの時　すでに 戦意を失っていた相手を
He'd already lost his will to fight
私は　殴ってしまった。
when I punched him.
これ以上　敗者にムチを打つような まねは　ごめんだ。
I will not fight someone who's lost.
ざけんなよ！ じゃあ　一体　どうする気だ！
Screw that! Then what do we do?
向こうは　決着がついてないって いって来てるんだぞ！
They're claiming that the
match hasn't ended!
彼に任せる。 はぁ？
Let him handle it. Huh?!
彼が目覚めれば おのずと答えは出るはず。
Once he wakes up,
we'll have our answer.
おいおい　ここから出るまでの 時間は限られているんだぞ！
Hey, now... We only have so much time left.
そんな悠長なことを いってる暇は…。
We can't afford to just sit and wait!
私から何かをする気は　ない。 お前な！
I have no intention of killing him! Come on!
ねぇ　あんたが嫌なら 俺が　やってやるよ。
Hey... If you don't want to dirty
your hands, I'll do it.
キルア？
Killua?
人を殺したこと　ないんでしょ？
You haven't ever killed
anyone before, right?
怖いの？
Are you scared?
殺しを「怖い」「怖くない」で 考えたことは　ない。
I have never considered whether
murder is frightening.
これは１対１の勝負 手出し無用だ。
But this is a one-on-one battle. You aren't permitted to interfere.
なるほどね。
Okay, then...
でもさ とにかく　団体行動なんだから わがままは　よくないぜ。
But we're working as a team, so you shouldn't be too selfish.
おっ　たまには いいこと　いうじゃねえか！
Oh! You do say useful things sometimes!
もっと　いったれ！ 他人の迷惑も考えろよな！
Keep it up! Don't you understand that you're
screwing up our chances?
悪いが 意見を変えるつもりは　ない。
I'm sorry, but I won't change my mind.
この強情っ張りが！
You stubborn fool...
よし　そんなら多数決だ！
Fine! A majority decision...
とどめを刺すなら「○」 刺さないなら「×」を押す。
O to kill him, and X to leave him alive.
せの！ フフフ…。
Ready, and...
何で　つかねえんだよ!?
Why isn't it working?!
俺達が　勝手に やってるからじゃない？
Maybe it's because we're
asking the question?
へ？
Huh?
試験として　向こうから 出題されてなきゃ ダメなんだろうな。
The watches only work for questions
presented by the examiners.
何…　なるほど　よし！
I see... Okay!
なら　挙手で決めようぜ！
Then we'll use a show of hands!
とどめを刺すほうに賛成の人？
Those who agree that he
should be finished off...
はい！
Now!
この裏切り者が！
You traitor...
さっき　クラピカに　一緒になって 説教したじゃねえか！
Weren't you just lecturing
Kurapika with me?
団体行動だろ！　団体行動！
We're supposed to be a team...
A team!
だって　無意味じゃん 「意見　変えない」っていってるし。
But it's pointless! He's not gonna change his mind.
おい　ゴン！ ゴンは　何で反対なんだよ？
Hey, Gon! Why do you oppose killing him?
確かに　クラピカの言う通り
Kurapika's right.
相手の人も　「俺の負け」って いいかけたしさ。
He was on the verge of surrendering.
起きるまで　待とうよ。
Let's wait for him to wake up.
ここは　やっぱり…。
I should just...
強制は　よくねえぜ。
You shouldn't force others to do things.
人それぞれの事情や信念が あるからなぁ。
Different people have different
circumstances and ideals.
おめぇの意見なんざ　聞いてねえ！
No one asked your opinion.
おいおい　多数決は みんなの意見を聞くもんだろ？
Hey... A majority ruling implies that you're
asking everyone's opinion.
くっ。 クッソ　分かったよ！ 勝手に　やっとけ！
Damn it! Fine! Do whatever you want!
レオリオ！
Leorio...
ったく　何だってんだ…。
Man, what's wrong with these people?
すねちゃった。
Now he's sulking.
早く進まなきゃ　意味ねえのによ 状況　分かってんのかよ！
None of this matters if we can't even progress. Don't you people get it?
とりあえず　ほっとこう。
Just leave him alone.
バカが！ 完全に　はまってやがる 多数決のトリックに
Fools... They've fallen for the trap
of the majority decision.
昨日今日　出会ったばかりの ５人が何かを決める時
You would expect it to be easier
for five people who've just met
多数決は　一見 便利で効率的に思える
to make decisions by majority rule.
また　個人の意見を 尊重しているようにも思えるが 実のところ　少数派の意思を 抹殺する危険な制度だ
While this method appears to
revere each individual opinion, in actuality, it suppresses the minority.
何度も連続して　少数派に回り 自分の意見が抹殺され続けたら
When a person consistently finds himself
in the minority, his opinion is always rejected.
疎外感　不満　怒りが 湧き上がって来て　対立を招く
His alienation, anger, and discontent lead to antagonism.
そして　チームの崩壊
Eventually, the team dissolves.
そもそも俺達は　試験を 受けに来た　ライバル同士だ
After all, we're rivals in
this Hunter Exam.
半ば強制的に 他人の意見に従わされ 窮地に追い込まれるなど
None of us would just
stand by and watch, as our chances were hurt
バカバカしくて 我慢できないはず
by someone else's dumb mistakes.
なのに　奴は 試験のムードに　のまれ やらなくていい場面にまで 多数決を持ち出して来た
But having been caught up in
the spirit of this test, he's begun using majority decision
in unrelated situations.
おまけに　多数決の時 論争を招く「相談」と並んで
And he made the mistake of holding a discussion before the vote.
最も　やってはならない 「挙手」で決めようとしやがった
He even used majority decision in its
worst form, a public show of hands.
タイマーのボタンを押して 決めるのと違い 誰が反対したのか分かる上に
Unlike when people press the buttons
of their own watches, everyone knows who diverged
from the majority.
自分が少数派になったら 反論が許されない最悪のシステム
So the minority can't even
protest the decision.
常に　特定の人物と 意見が対立し 一方だけが意思を 抹殺されるようなことが続けば 集団は決裂
When someone feels they have no say, and that their opinions are
constantly rejected, the group breaks down.
俺達の場合　それは ５人全員の失格を意味する
In this case, it means all five of us will fail the exam.
時間の問題だな　フフフ…
It's just a matter of time.
向こうは何か 険悪ムードみたいだね。
The atmosphere on the
other side is gloomy.
待っていたぜ
I've been waiting for you...
ヒソカ。
...Hisoka.
今年は試験官ではなく リベンジャーとしてな。
I'm not an examiner this year. I'm here for revenge.
去年の試験以来 貴様を殺すことだけを考えて来た。
Since last year's exam, all I've focused on was killing you.
この傷の恨み
Today, I'll get payback
今日こそ晴らす！
for my scars!
フッ　君が試験官として 能力が足りなかっただけのこと。
Hmph. Those scars merely show that you
were an incompetent examiner.
それを「逆恨み」っていうんだよ。
You're blaming me for your
own inadequacies.
ほざけ！
Keep yapping!
フフフ…　覚悟しろよ。
Prepare to die.
二刀流か…　あっ。
Dual wielding?
無限四刀流！
Infinite quad wielding!
くらえ！
Take this...
まだまだ！
It's not over yet!
ハハハ！　上下左右 正面背後　逃げ場は　ない！
Up, down, left, right. Front and back... You have nowhere to run!
あらゆる角度から 無数のやいばが貴様を切り刻む！
You'll be cut from every angle,
by my endless stream of blades.
この無限攻撃をかわすのは 不可能！
Dodging my infinite attack waves
is impossible!
苦痛に　もがいて　のたうち回れ！
I'll have you writhe in pain...
そして　死ねぇ！　ヒソカ！
...until you die, Hisoka!
確かに　よけるのは難しそうだ。
It would indeed be difficult
to dodge your attacks.
バカな…　俺は飛んで来る刀を 受けられるようになるまで 半年以上かかったんだぞ！
Impossible... It took me over half a year
to master catching those blades!
なんだ。
Oh...
思ったより簡単なんだ。
It was easier than anticipated.
無駄な努力　ご苦労さま。
I appreciate your futile efforts.
クソ！
Damn it!
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]　４４番ヒソカ。 [ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]　３次試験通過　第１号！
Hisoka, applicant #44, is the first
to pass the Third Phase.
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]　所要時間６時間１７分。
Total time, six hours and
seventeen minutes.
チッ。
Tsk...
どうかしたのか？　ゴン。 うん。
Is something wrong, Gon? Uh-huh.
なるほどね。
I get it...
あのさ。 ん？
Hey...
もしかして　あいつ もう死んでるんじゃないの？
It's quite possible that
he's already dead.
何だと？
What's that?
だって　随分　時間経つのに あれきり　全然　動かないんだ。
Well, it's been several hours, and he hasn't moved an inch.
クソ…
Damn...
遠くて　こっちからじゃ よく分かんねえな。
It's too far away for us to tell.
おい！　そいつの生死を 確認させてもらおうか！
Hey! We want to check his body!
急に　何？
What's that?
気絶どころか　とっくに 死んでっかもしれねえからな。
He could already be dead.
さっきも　いったでしょ？ 彼は気絶しているだけよ。
I already told you,
he's only unconscious.
あれから　何時間　経ってると 思ってるんだ！
How many hours has it been?
お前の言葉だけじゃ 信用できねえな。
I can't just take your word for it!
それじゃ　賭けましょうか？
Then let's make a bet.
賭け？　賭けって何を？
A bet? On what?
彼が生きているか 死んでいるか…。
On whether he's dead or alive.
一体　何を賭けるってんだ！
What would we wager?
時間よ。
Time.
時間？
Time?
私と　あなたの勝負は　賭け ギャンブル。
We will settle our match through
a betting game, a gamble.
時間をチップ代わりにね。
And we'll use time, rather than chips.
壁のモニターを見て。
Look at the monitor on the wall.
使える時間は　お互い ５０時間ずつ。
We each have fifty hours.
ただし　賭けるのは １０時間単位でしか使えない。
However, we can only wager
multiples of ten.
どちらかの時間が　ゼロになるまで 賭け続ける。
We continue placing bets until one
of us has no hours left.
時間を賭けた勝負…。
A match where we gamble time...
賭けの問題は 交互に出題すること。
We'll take turns deciding
what to bet on.
そっちの時間が ゼロになったら タワー脱出のリミットは ５０時間　短くなる。
If you end up with zero hours, your time limit will also be
shortened by fifty hours.
そっちがゼロになったら？
And if you end up with zero hours?
この勝負を受けるなら 彼の生死を確認させてあげる。
If these terms are acceptable, I'll check whether he's still alive.
レルート…。
Leroute...
希少生物販売　および 賭博法違反等で
Serving a 112-year sentence
懲役１１２年か。
for endangered species trafficking
and illegal gambling.
いかにも彼女らしい 勝負方法だね。
This match sounds like
her kind of game.
ったく　イカレた女だぜ。
Man, this chick is whack.
てめぇの刑期を賭けるとはな。
She's willing to risk extending
her own sentence.
慎重に答えろよ　レオリオ。
Consider your answer carefully, Leorio.
もし負けたら　いきなり タワー脱出の残り時間が
If you lose, we'll have
fifty fewer hours
９時間ほどに減るぞ。
with which to escape the tower.
てめぇに　いわれたくねえな！
You shouldn't talk...
本はといえば お前が　とどめを刺さねえから いけねえんだろうが！
After all, this is your fault,
for not finishing him off!
分かった ならば　もう　何も　いうまい。
Fine! I won't say another word!
フン！ もう…　仲間割れは　よそうよ！
Hey, we shouldn't fight
amongst ourselves!
フフっ　その調子　その調子…
Keep fighting, keep fighting...
よし！　その勝負　受けるぜ！
Right! I accept!
ＯＫ！ 最初は私が出題したから 「生きている」「死んでいる」の どちらに　何時間　賭けるかは
Okay! I chose our first bet, so you can decide how
many hours we'll wager
あなたが決めていいわよ。
on whether he's alive or dead.
生きてるほうに　１０時間！
I bet ten hours that he's alive.
散々「死んでるんじゃねえか」とか いっておきながら…。
What's this? You were the one whining
over his being dead.
フフフ…！ それじゃあ　いいわ　確認して。
Very well. Then let's check.
結構　慎重だな。
You're being pretty cautious...
何も　喋らねえんじゃ なかったのか？
Weren't you going to not
say anything else?
１０時間ね…
Ten hours, huh?
当然じゃねえか
This was the obvious choice.
仮に　これで外れても 奴の死さえ確認できれば クラピカの勝利が確定する
Even if I'm wrong, as long as we confirm his death, Kurapika will have won his round.
死んでるほうに賭けて 気絶してるだけだったら 踏んだり蹴ったりだからな
If he's really unconscious, I'll just kick his ass.
確かにな…。
So it seems.
よし！
All right...
まずは　レオリオがリードしたね。
Leorio has the lead!
マズいな…。 え？
This is bad. Huh?
あいつ　このまま　ずっと 目覚めないかもしれないぜ。
It's possible he isn't going to wake up.
何が　いいたい？
What do you mean?
さっき　あの女が　倒れてる奴に 近づいて行っただろ？
Remember when that woman walked near the guy on the floor?
それで？ あの時点で
What of it? I thought then
もう死んでたんじゃないかと 思ったんだけど
that he was already dead.
考えてみれば　死んでるよりも 生きていて　起きないほうが あいつらにしてみれば 都合が　いいんだよね。
But on second thought, they'd obviously prefer him alive, but remaining unconscious.
残り時間　あいつが ずっと起きなかったら それだけで　７２年分の刑期が 縮まるんだから。
If he doesn't wake up
before the test ends, it shortens their sentences
by seventy-two years.
じゃあ　あいつが ずっと起きなかったら　俺達…。
So if he doesn't wake up...
だから　いってるだろ！
That's my point!
あいつら 最初から　そのつもりで…。
That's been their intention all along.
さぁ　次は　あんたの番よ 賭けの問題を決めてちょうだい。
Well, it's your turn. Decide what we'll bet on.
そうだな…。
Let's see...
こいつが本当に 気絶してるかどうか　賭けようぜ！
How about we bet on whether
he's truly unconscious?
えっ？
Huh?
なるほど。 ふん。
I see.
おい… どうすりゃいいんだ？
Hey, what am I supposed to do?
こんなのメモに　なかったぜ
The note didn't cover this.
俺が目覚めた時 そばにあったメモには
When I woke up, a note next to me
「気絶したフリを続けろ!! このメモは　口の中に隠せ!!」と 書いてあった
told me to feign unconsciousness, and to hide the note in my mouth.
すぐに　ピンと来たぜ
I understood the plan immediately.
このまま　たぬき寝入りで 時間をつぶせば ７２年分の懲役が 帳消しになるとな
If I can buy time by pretending
to be asleep, our sentences will be shortened
by seventy-two years!
え？　どっちだ？
So, then what do I do?
このまま 起きなくていいのか？
Should I stay down?
いいわよ 本当に気絶しているほうに ２０時間　賭けるわ！
Very well. I bet twenty hours that he
really is unconscious.
ＯＫ！　分かったぜ
Okay, got it...
俺は　このまま 気絶したフリを続けるぜ！
I'm supposed to keep acting
like I'm unconscious!
でも　本当に 気絶してるかどうか どうやって確かめるつもり？
But how do we confirm whether
he's really unconscious?
なに…。
Oh...
簡単さ！
That's simple.
チッ　重てぇな…。
This guy's heavy...
こいつを　ここから下へ落とす。
I'll just toss him off the edge.
何じゃ　そりゃあ!?
Wh-What the hell?!
本当に気絶してるなら そのまま　すんなり落ちて 死ぬはずだ。
If he's actually unconscious, he'll fall to his death.
気は確かなの？
Are you insane?
まだ　彼は 前の勝負が　ついてないのよ？
His match hasn't been settled yet.
そんな方法　認められないわ。
We can't accept those terms.
安心しな もし　こいつが落ちて死ねば こっち側の反則負けってことで トータル　そっちの２勝だ。
Don't worry. If he falls and dies, we'll forfeit the match, which will give you two wins.
それで文句ないだろ？
Is that satisfactory?
そうね…　文句ないわ。
Yes, it is.
何だと！ ふざけんじゃねえぜ！
What was that? Don't be ridiculous...
俺の命を 何だと思ってやがんだ！
We're talking about my life here!
その代わり　変更するわ。
But then I'm changing my wager.
彼が本当に気絶していないほうに ４０時間。
I bet forty hours that he
isn't unconscious.
残り全部を賭けることにする。
Everything I have left.
フッ　女狐 ようやく尻尾を出しやがったな。
Heh, little sneak. Finally showing your true colors.
それじゃ　離すぜ…。
Then, I'll let go of him.
うわ!!　待て待て！ 起きてる！　起きてるよ!!
Whoa! Wait! I'm awake! I'm awake...
離すな！ うぅ…。
Don't let go!
うわ！　ちょ…　うわ！
Wait! Whoa...
落ちる!!
I'm gonna fall!
おはようさん　フッ。
Good morning.
イカレてるぜ　お前ら！
You people are crazy.
付き合ってられるか！
I've had enough!
勝負は　俺の負けで結構だ！
I'll take the loss!
恩赦なんざ　クソくらえだ！
Forget the sentence reduction!
刑務所のほうが よっぽど安全だぜ！　まったく。
It's safer in prison...
分かってたのね あいつが起きてたこと。
You knew that he was awake.
これでも医者志望なんでな。
I actually aspire to become a doctor.
眼球運動を　ちょいと調べりゃ 分かるさ。
All I had to do was check
his eye movement.
でも　これで　そっちのチップは 残り２０時間。
However, you're down
to twenty hours.
だが　勝負自体は　２勝１敗で こっちがリーチだ。
But now we have a 2-1 lead.
さぁ　次は　そっちの番だ！
Now... It's your turn!
賭けの問題を出してもらおうか。
What do you want to bet on?
マジタニが負けを認め これで ２勝１敗となった　ゴン達
Majitani surrenders, giving Gon and his friends a 2-1 lead.
だが　時間を使った賭けは ８０対２０と　差をつけられる
However, in the time-betting match, they're down 80-20.
果たして　レルートが出す 次の問題とは？
What will Leroute choose to bet on?